export const MathBasic=[
  {
    question: "19 + = 42",
    Options: ["23", "61", "0", "42"],
    correct: 1,
    marked: -1
  },
  {
    question: "What is the symbol of pi?",
    Options: ["€", "π", "Ω", "0∞"],
    correct: 2,
    marked: -1
  },
  {
    question: "Arrange the numbers in ascending order: 7, 36, 12, 29, 21",
    Options: ["36, 29, 21, 12, 7", "36, 29, 7, 21, 12", "7, 12, 21, 29, 36", "None of these"],
    correct: 3,
    marked: -1
  },
  {
    question: "What is the greatest two digit number?",
    Options: ["10", "90", "11", "99"],
    correct: 4,
    marked: -1
  },
  {
    question: "How much is 90 - 19?",
    Options: ["71", "109", "89", "None of these"],
    correct: 1,
    marked: -1
  },
  {
    question: "20 is divisible by ...",
    Options: ["1", "3", "7", "None of these"],
    correct: 1,
    marked: -1
  },
  {
    question: "Find the value of x; if x = (2 x 3) + 11.",
    Options: ["55", "192", "17", "66"],
    correct: 3,
    marked: -1
  },
  {
    question: "What is the smallest three digit number?",
    Options: ["100", "999", "111", "101"],
    correct: 1,
    marked: -1
  },
  {
    question: "How much is 190 - 87 + 16?",
    Options: ["103", "261", "87", "119"],
    correct: 4,
    marked: -1
  },
  {
    question: "What is 1000 x 1 equal to?",
    Options: ["1", "1000", "0", "None of these"],
    correct: 2,
    marked: -1
  },
  
    {
      question: "In 24,673; the place-value of 6 is",
      Options: ["700", "600", "10", "100"],
      correct: 2,
      marked: -1
    },
    {
      question: "In 24,673; the face-value of 4 is",
      Options: ["4", "2", "1000", "9999"],
      correct: 1,
      marked: -1
    },
    {
      question: "The least number of two digits is ...",
      Options: ["99", "11", "90", "None of these"],
      correct: 4,
      marked: -1
    },
    {
      question: "The largest number of six digits is",
      Options: ["9,99,999", "1,00,000", "1,11,111", "1,11,000"],
      correct: 1,
      marked: -1
    },
    {
      question: "The smallest number of seven digits is",
      Options: ["0", "99,99,999", "10,10,100", "10,00,000"],
      correct: 4,
      marked: -1
    },
    {
      question: "The difference between the smallest number of four digits and the largest number of three digits is",
      Options: ["1", "100", "0", "999"],
      correct: 1,
      marked: -1
    },
    {
      question: "The sum of the least number of three digits and largest number of two digits is",
      Options: ["101", "199", "111", "100"],
      correct: 2,
      marked: -1
    },
    {
      question: "If a number has an even number or zero its unit place; the number is always divisible by",
      Options: ["2", "5", "3", "7"],
      correct: 1,
      marked: -1
    },
    {
      question: "A number is divisible by 3 if the sum of its digits is divisible by",
      Options: ["1", "2", "3", "5"],
      correct: 3,
      marked: -1
    },
    {
      question: "A number is divisible by 5 if its unit digit is",
      Options: ["2 or 0", "10 or 0", "0 or 5", "None of these"],
      correct: 3,
      marked: -1
    }
]
